fvdtube.com 2019-07-12

# Privacy Policy

Here at Fvdtube.com / Fvdtube App. We are aware that our users care and are cautious about how their personal information is used and shared. Your privacy is our utmost concern and we take it very seriously, please be assured. Kindly read the following Privacy Policy to learn more about our Terms & Conditions.

Using or visiting the services of the app in any manner acknowledges that you accept all the policies and practices outlined here in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby declare that we can process, use, collect and share your personal data as pronounced herein.

We hereby declare that we abide by the **EUGDPR** (General Data Protection Regulation), which has been recently implemented in European Union.

**1\. Privacy Policy Principles**

Following are the three Principles that this Privacy Policy holds in relation to providing you with the relative services from our end.

Information collected will only be used for the purpose of improving our services.

You may deliver and we only gather “Personal Information” that helps identify ‘you’ personally, in order to provide Services in a much more optimized way.

We promise to keep transparency in our privacy practices.

**2\. What does this privacy policy consist of?**

The information gathered from our users while they are accessing or using our Services is covered in this Privacy Policy.

This privacy policy does not cover protection of information from the companies that we DO NOT own or control or the entities that we do not manage or employ, including, without any limitations, the third-party content providers that provide you the information through the services.

The company has a strict policy against the registration. We do not allow knowingly to collect or implore Personal Information or allow to register any individual under the age of 13. Kindly do not attempt to register yourself or send any Personal Information to us, if you are under 13, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In such cases that we learn about the collected information is from an under 13 children, and without any parental consent, we delete that information rapidly. Please contact us at admin@fvdtube.com, if you believe that our website might persist of any such information filled about or from any under 13 children.

**3\. What kind of information we collect and why?**

We generally place the collected information into two categories:

The user data collected from the services used

Collective data about the content user engages with. The information collected is used for improving and personalizing our services, to evaluate how you use our services and to provide you with your products and services. We may share this information with our partners, to help you provide an optimal experience from our services, but never disclose your personal identity. Here are a few gathered examples of our services used by the users.

Here are the details about the personal information we collect from the users:

**Country Code:** We seek this information about your geographical domains to serve you in a way better way in future (in our next releases) by providing the region-specific music to you.

**Storage Permission:** We ask the storage permission (read and write permission) in order to analyze and save those downloaded files on your devices.

Although we have taken all the data safety and integrity measures to protect your personal information, still if any third party anyhow intrudes and try to fetch this information unlawfully, then this privacy policy, in that case, will not be liable.

How can you access and control your information?

When it is about your personal information, then you have some options available to you that are

mentioned below along with the method for exercising them and any limitations.

What options do you get?

You have an absolute right to request for a copy of your personal information, to ask for restriction or removal of your information, to questions usage of your information by us (that also includes promotional purposes), or to ask for your information in electronic or structured manner. In case of any assistance, you can contact us by sending an email which is given below in the queries section.

**Access/update your information**

You can access or update your information, in this regard our service and its related documentation offer options on how you can access and update certain details about you using the Service itself. In order to make changes to your profile information easily, you can use the profile settings.

**Remove or disable your account**

If you have decided not to use our services any longer, then you have option to disable or delete your account. You can access the account removal settings within the account settings of your account. If you find any trouble removing your account from the account settings, then you can request us to remove your account. For this, you will need to send us an email requesting the removal.

**Request to remove your information**

There is an easy option for removing certain information about you from the Service itself. For instance, you can remove your profile details from the profile settings.

**Request to stop the usage of your details**

In any case, if you consider that without having the appropriate rights we are using, accessing, stopping or otherwise processing your information, then you have right to send us a request for stopping these activities. For example, if there is a service account that was created for you for which you did not give your permission and have no idea, then you can send us request us to stop using your information. To send us a request you can use our email which is given below under the queries section.

**4\. We do not disclose the personal information to others, what we collect from users**

We intentionally never share your personal information with anyone who/which is not related anyway to our products or services. Your personal information remains protected in our databases.

**5\. Disclaimer regarding personal information security**

All the sensitive personal information you provide, will be in a highly encrypted format to make your identity safe and secure in our databases. We sometimes may provide you with some third-party links on our website to make your experience better. These given websites have their own specific Privacy Policies; hence we have no such liability for the activities and content. Although we always welcome any kind of feedback related to them.

**6\. When you are visiting our website from anywhere**

If you are using our application from anywhere in the world, your personal information may be relocated or stored to our main and other servers as well. All these data and information will be in encrypted form to make your privacy more secure.

**7\. Amendments to the Privacy Policy**

We keep amending the Privacy Policy time-to-time. Therefore, the usage of information is totally subject to these changes. If we make any in the process we share or use your personal information, we would surely notify you through emails and you would be supposed to abide by these changes.

**8\. Here is how you can opt-out the information you have shared with us? You can remove or modify the information as well**

You need to drop us a message mentioning your account preferences so that we could be able to delete all the stored online information from our databases. Please write us at **admin@fvdtube.com** With reference to the applicable laws, we would request you to consider that we might keep the info about individual sales transaction for record keeping.

**9\. For any security breach, there is a consent to electronic notice**

If we ever need to send unauthorized access notice or any other security system related invasion here, you agree that we may do so whenever it is required (or voluntarily) by just posting a notice on our website or sending a notice to any provided email address we have for you, in our (or their) good faith discretion. You also agree that this notice sent to you will always be counted as a notice to others for whom you are acting and agree to pass the notice on to them.

**10\. Concerns or Queries**

If you ever have any kind of concern or query related to the privacy policies, kindly feel free to drop us a message explaining the same to admin@fvdtube.com We will make sure to resolve your query as soon as possible.

**Email us at admin@fvdtube.com**
